{
    "subject": "Prince_Ren\u00e9_of_Bourbon-Parma",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Princess_Margaret_of_Denmark",
    "human_readable": "Prince Ren\u00e9 of Bourbon-Parma is married to Princess Margaret of Denmark.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9481636881828308,
            "question": "To whom is Prince Ren\u00e9 of Bourbon-Parma married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9459657669067383,
            "question": "What is the name of the princess married to Prince Ren\u00e9 of Bourbon-Parma?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9297345280647278,
            "question": "What is the name of the prince who is married to Princess Margaret of Denmark?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9244388937950134,
            "question": "What is the full name of the prince who is married to Princess Margaret of Denmark?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9221750497817993,
            "question": "Who is married to Princess Margaret of Denmark?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9140457510948181,
            "question": "Is Princess Margaret of Denmark married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7435882687568665,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Prince Ren\u00e9 of Bourbon-Parma?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6637023091316223,
            "question": "Which royal family does Princess Margaret of Denmark belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6605045795440674,
            "question": "Is Prince Ren\u00e9 of Bourbon-Parma a member of royalty?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17688554525375366,
            "question": "Who are the individuals involved in this marriage?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Prince Ren\u00e9 of Bourbon-Parma is married to Princess Margaret of Denmark.",
            "html": "yago_31433_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Prince Ren\u00e9 of Bourbon-Parma a member of royalty?",
            "html": "yago_31433_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which royal family does Princess Margaret of Denmark belong to?",
            "html": "yago_31433_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of Prince Ren\u00e9 of Bourbon-Parma?",
            "html": "yago_31433_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31433_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31433_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31433_134.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31433_142.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31433_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31433_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31433_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31433_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31433_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31433_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Prince Ren\u00e9 of Bourbon-Parma is married to Princess Margaret of Denmark. The Wedding Ball of Prince Ren\u00e9 and Princess Margaret is described, along with their children, and it's stated that they were married until his death in 1962."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide clear information supporting that Princess Margaret of Denmark was married to Prince Ren\u00e9 of Bourbon-Parma. Multiple sources in the provided context confirm their marriage and details about it, thus affirming the stated triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}